{
    "subject": "resource/Summitville,_New_York",
    "predicate": "property/subdivisionName",
    "object": "resource/New_York",
    "human_readable": "Summitville, New York is a part of New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8527863621711731,
            "question": "What state is Summitville part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8487563729286194,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Summitville, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218072056770325,
            "question": "Where is Summitville located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8115859627723694,
            "question": "Is Summitville a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6056817770004272,
            "question": "What is the history of Summitville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5708437561988831,
            "question": "What is the population of Summitville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569801330566406,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or attractions in Summitville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4928513467311859,
            "question": "Is Summitville a good place to live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42976635694503784,
            "question": "What is the geography like in Summitville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4219585359096527,
            "question": "Does Summitville have a local government?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Summitville, New York is a part of New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9230_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geography like in Summitville?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9230_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Summitville a good place to live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9230_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks or attractions in Summitville?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9230_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9230_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information in the documents supports the triple. According to the documents, Summitville is located in Sullivan County, New York, United States (document 3), which implies that it is a part of New York."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the geographical location of Summitville, which is in Sullivan County, New York. While they do not explicitly state that Summitville is part of New York, it can be inferred from the context that Summitville is indeed located within the state of New York."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}